https://www.visionmetrics.net/en/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentPrivacy Policyadmin2020-09-04T10:31:08+01:00At Vision Metrics we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.This policy explains when and why we collect personal information about people who visit our website, how we use it, the conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure.
We have updated our Terms of Service and our Privacy Policy effective May 25, 2018. The updates are mainly to address GDRP European based users. This update includes several changes, including but not limited to changes necessary to meet these requirements and are in supplement to the standard terms & service Vision Metrics offers.Any questions regarding our privacy policy can be sent to contact@visionmetrics.net.Vision Metrics strives to make our privacy policy as simple and transparent as possible and strives to be fully GDRP compliant, Vision Metrics sets forth to address the following aspects of the GDRP.• What information is being collected?
• Who is collecting it?
• How is it collected?
• Why is it being collected?
• How will it be used?
• Who will it be shared with?Who are we?We’re Vision Metrics a global software platform otherwise known as Software as a Service (SaaS) enabling and helping organizations process and analyze employee and company performance feedback metrics. We are headquarter in the Netherlands. Weteringschans 165, 1017 XD Amsterdam, the Netherlands and can always be contacted at contact@visionmetrics.netHow do we collect information from you?We obtain information about you when you visit out website, register to our resource center/store section and request additional services in our resource center/store section. If you become a customer or are an employee of a customer organization using your employee portal.What type of information is collected from you?The personal information we collect might include your name, address, email address, IP address, and information regarding what pages are accessed and when. If you purchase a product from us, your card information is not identifiably stored with us, it is collected by our third-party payment processor (Stripe), who specializes in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions.Google Analytics. We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of our Website Services (e.g., Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit the Website Services, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the Website Services). Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date that you visit the Website Services, rather than your name or other identifying information. The information collected through the use of Google Analytics is not combined with your Personal Information.· Learn more about how Google Analytics collects and processes data and opt-out options at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/Mailchimp. We use a mailing service called  ‘Mailchimp’ to send transactional and marketing related emails to customers. When signing on to our website resource center registration and contact form you are signing into our mailchimp list which you can control with opt out options and removal via request (emailing us). We will expand upon this functionality in the future.If you are a customer or a feedback provider employee of a customer, the customer or your employer may enter additional data about your, i.e. Job title, department you work etc. If you are a user and of an organization or you have been invited by an organization to provide feedback and have questions or are concerned, we welcome you to reach out to us.
How is your information used.We may use your information to:– Process orders that you have submitted;
– To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into by you and us;
– Seek your views or comments on the services we provide;
– Notify you of changes to our services;
– Send you communications which you have requested and that may be of interest to you. These may include information about campaigns, appeals, promotions of our core services.From time to time we review our retention periods regarding personal data. We are legally required to hold some types of information to fulfil our statutory obligations. We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity, or as long as is set out in any relevant contract you hold with us.Who has access to your information?We do not sell or rent your information to third parties.
We do not share your information with third parties for their marketing purposes.Third Party Service Providers working on our behalf: We may pass your information to our third-party service providers for the purposes of completing tasks and providing services to you on our behalf (for example to process the sending of mailings and or mailings we send on your behalf or transactional mailings required to operate your account with us). However, when we use third party service providers, we disclose only the personal information that is necessary to deliver the service. Please be reassured that we will not release your information to third parties beyond the scope of Vision Metrics for them to use for their own direct marketing purposes unless we are required to do so by law, for example, by a court order or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime.We may transfer your personal information to a third party as part of a sale of some or all of our business and assets to any third party or as part of any business restructuring or reorganization, or if we’re under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation or to enforce or apply our terms of use or to protect the rights, property or safety of our supporters and customers.Your choicesYou have a choice about whether or not you wish to receive information from us. We will not contact you for marketing purposes by post if you have indicated that you do not wish to be contacted. You can change your marketing preferences at any time by contacting us by email: contact@visionmetrics.net.Opting-Out of Marketing Communications. We provide a means to unsubscribe in our marketing-related email communications. Note that we will continue to send transaction-related emails regarding products or services that you have requested following an unsubscribe. We may also need to send you certain communications regarding operation and administration of the Services, and you will not be able to opt out of those communications, e.g., communications regarding updates to our Terms of Use or this Policy. If you no longer desire to be contacted by us, you must terminate your relationship with Vision Metrics and can no longer use our Services.Rights in your information. Access, rectification, erasure and restriction.In accordance with applicable law, you may have the right to (a) request confirmation of whether we store, use or share any of your Personal Information; (b) obtain access to or a copy of your Personal Information; (c) receive an electronic copy of Personal Information that you have provided to us, or ask us to send that information to another company (the “right of data portability”); (d) restrict our uses of your Personal Information or, as described above, object to those uses; (e) seek correction of inaccurate, untrue or incomplete Personal Information; or (f) request erasure of Personal Information held about you by Vision Metrics, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at the e-mail or physical addresses set out in the who we are section.We will process such requests in accordance with local laws. To protect your privacy, Vision Metrics will take steps to verify your identity before granting access or making any changes to your Personal Information.You have the right to ask for a copy of the information Vision Metrics hold about you (we may charge EUR15 for information requests) to cover our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you).How you can access and update your informationThe accuracy of your information is important to us. We’re working on ways to make it easier for you to review and correct the information that we hold about you. In the meantime, if you change email address, or any of the other information we hold is inaccurate or out of date, please email us at: contact@visionmetrics.net.RetentionVision Metrics will retain your Personal Information for as long as you have a relationship with us, and for a period after your relationship with us has ended. More…· When determining how long this retention period will last, we take into account the length of time Personal Information is required to:
· Continue to develop, tailor, upgrade and improve our Services;
· Maintain business records for analysis and/or audit purposes;Security precautions in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your information.When you give us personal information, we take steps to ensure that it’s treated securely. Any sensitive information (such as credit or debit card details) is encrypted and protected with the following software 128 Bit encryption on SSL. When you are on a secure page, a lock icon will appear on the bottom of web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer.Non-sensitive details (your email address etc.) are transmitted normally over the Internet, and this can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Where we have given (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our websites, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.Registered Clients
When a potential visitor of the site becomes a paying customer, Vision Metrics will proceed as a ‘processor’ entity. Some terms and guidelines will change under a processing framework.Review of this PolicyWe keep this Policy under regular review and will update accordingly from time to time.Contact Information:
VISION METRICS
Weteringschans 165
1017 XD Amsterdam
Email: contact@visionmetrics.net
Go to Top
